[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "I mean, historically, since the Second World War, say, is there evidence to say that when you go really negative against a vulnerable opponent perhaps, you'll win?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Not necessarily.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "I mean -- I don't think the gloves have come off here, have they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "It's tamed and it's a mediocre as a piece of advertising.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Which is probably the sign of a good one, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "CD", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "RBR", ":", "WDT", "VBZ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "Would you go there if you were Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Well -- I guess that's one hot issue, but I would say there's something even more -- which is people don't really know who Romney is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rubio"]}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "What do you make of it or what's going on behind the scenes here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "My guess is that Rubio indeed will not be the vice presidential nominee.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "Who's the smart pick?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "ICH: I don't think there really is a smart pick.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Am I right to be that cynical?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Probably, but I have a feeling in this case it's pretty small potatoes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"], "PERSON": ["Andrew Jackson"]}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "How justified is the criticism?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Well, first of all, this is an historical battle within the Constitution going back to Andrew Jackson who defied Congress and said you pass the law, now you execute it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Why wouldn't they just be coming out with it otherwise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "So the constitutional principle versus the political reality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House"]}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "What do you think will happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "I think that the House will not vote contempt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Frank"]}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Michael Steele, former chairman of the RNC, Republican National Committee, criticizes Mitt Romney for taking a Barack Obama statement that he doesn't know anything about the economy when he was referring to John McCain taking it out of context and then Mitt Romney says well, if it was out of context, what's sauce for the goose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "To be fair to Frank, I don't think he likes the negative ads.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["RNC", "Republican National Committee", "Barack Obama"], "PERSON": ["Michael Steele", "Mitt Romney", "John McCain", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama", "Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", "RBR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Can a presidential candidate win through positivity alone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Well, it isn't necessarily -- the answer is yes, but contrasting, I think, Barack Obama's ideas are better than Mitt Romney's.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "All of these skills are pretty seriously tested in this case because eon the face of it it's pretty grim for Penn State, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Well, first let me say, I have to be very limited in what I can say to you about this, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Penn State"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Is that the problem for Penn State, that when you have such an iconic character, with Joe Paterno, for example, wielding such power through his just years of experience, decades of experience, that if it turns out that Sandusky is guilty and gets wayed (ph) off for a long time and it's sort of confirmed again that Joe Paterno knew and others knew, that that brings shame to Penn State, doesn't it, just an institution, that more young boys were allowed to be abused simply because those in positions of authority, for whatever reason, didn't do anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "NNS", "VBD", "CD", "NN", ":", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "CC", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJR", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Look, just to be clear, to protect myself, I didn't know we would be talking about this subject tonight.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Penn State", "Penn State"], "LOCATION": ["Sandusky"], "PERSON": ["Joe Paterno", "Joe Paterno"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJR", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Do you think there's been a seismic shock to the whole system in this country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Well, without focusing on just higher education, I think a good part of government's problem is an absence of transparency.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Google"]}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "What is the kind of interview that absolutely sends you demented?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "It's -- they Google.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "What do you think of America right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "You're starting right off there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "How much has that guided your sense of people not being reliant on their parents?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "That's a really good question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Are you an Obama man at heart?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "What is the kind of leader that you're craving in an American president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Moral compass.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "I agree.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "IN", "CD", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Do you want to name how many you've rolled in the hay with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "More than one and less than five.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Did you actually roll in the hay with her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "She actually has a hay bale in her bedroom.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Why shouldn't their opinion, their Tweets be as valuable to the world as yours or mine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "I have no problem with that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'90s"]}, "docId": "120620pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", ":", "WDT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "What do you feel about this album?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "What's interesting about it in my life is I made some great albums in the '90s and -- which become sort of almost like a mill stone around my neck.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]